<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<RecentObjects>
  <RecentFeatureCollections>Current MSMS feature search,MSFC000405,MSFC000322,MSFC000321,MSFC000442,MSFC000409,MSFC000361</RecentFeatureCollections>
  <RecentClusterSets>M2CDS00341,M2CDS00365</RecentClusterSets>
  <RecentExperiments>
    <experimentPointer projectType="DATA_ANALYSIS" id="30d1ad8f-6176-42f2-9012-4321c1b9e5a8" name="EX01332 - Starr County BATCH02" description="Metabolomics on 600 individuals from Starr County, Texas, 300 with normal glycemia and 300 with prediabetes at six time points over three years, at baseline and 3, 6, 12, 24, 36 months after." experimentFile="y:\dataanalysis\mrc2toolboxprojects\_core\ex01332\ex01332-starr-county-batch02\ex01332-starr-county-batch02.caproject" dateCreated="2024-03-01 13:54:50" lastModified="2024-03-18 19:57:50" limsExperiment="EX01332" />
    <experimentPointer projectType="DATA_ANALYSIS" id="52fa83c8-a8af-4324-9bbf-c8f5fbef4c44" name="EX01392 - Starr CountyBatch-01 5ul" description="Metabolomics on 600 individuals from Starr County, Texas, 300 with normal glycemia and 300 with prediabetes at six time points over three years, at baseline and 3, 6, 12, 24, 36 months after." experimentFile="y:\dataanalysis\mrc2toolboxprojects\_core\ex01392\ex01392-starr-countybatch-01-5ul\ex01392-starr-countybatch-01-5ul.caproject" dateCreated="2024-03-20 15:09:02" lastModified="2024-03-22 16:01:21" limsExperiment="EX01392" />
    <experimentPointer projectType="DATA_ANALYSIS" id="a67f3b78-4399-4a89-959c-1e8bbccbb453" name="Dup-removal-test" description="Dup-removal-test" experimentFile="y:\dataanalysis\mrc2toolboxprojects\_core\dup-removal-test\dup-removal-test.caproject" dateCreated="2024-03-25 16:02:17" lastModified="2024-03-25 16:14:06" />
    <experimentPointer projectType="DATA_ANALYSIS" id="68875373-c3b3-4f9c-a618-c2dfc4944cdb" name="Recent exp test" description="Recent exp test" experimentFile="Y:\DataAnalysis\MRC2ToolboxProjects\_CORE\Recent-exp-test\Recent-exp-test.caproject" dateCreated="2024-03-26 12:34:47" lastModified="2024-03-26 12:34:48" />
    <experimentPointer projectType="DATA_ANALYSIS" id="60714c0a-d810-426e-82d4-7df7e6cc4c04" name="EX01392 - Starr CountyBatch 2" description="Metabolomics on 600 individuals from Starr County, Texas, 300 with normal glycemia and 300 with prediabetes at six time points over three years, at baseline and 3, 6, 12, 24, 36 months after." experimentFile="Y:\DataAnalysis\MRC2ToolboxProjects\_CORE\EX01392\EX01392-Starr-CountyBatch-2\EX01392-Starr-CountyBatch-2.caproject" dateCreated="2024-03-29 14:04:35" lastModified="2024-03-29 14:04:36" limsExperiment="EX01392" />
    <experimentPointer projectType="DATA_ANALYSIS" id="fece420f-368f-482b-b5ce-c9a850be53d9" name="EX01413 - 202401_YG_Cells" description="Dear he or she, the estimated sample sizes amount to 110, with 40 being cultured adhesive human aortic smooth muscle cells submitted on a 10cm plate, and the remainder consisting of mouse plasma. While the final number may vary, we assure you it will be more than 101. Concerning cell samples, there are two distinct experiments?Exp1 designed as 2X2, and Exp2 designed as 2X3. Despite their differences, we request both cell experiments to be prepared and detected in the same batch for potential future raw data analysis. For analysis, please analyze the two separately. Plasma samples involve three experiments (Exp3 and Exp5 designed as 2X2, and Exp4 with only one factor and three conditions). For two-factor experiments, we aim to observe differences between groups and interactions, while for single-factor experiments, we seek to identify differences." experimentFile="y:\dataanalysis\mrc2toolboxprojects\_core\ex01413-202401_yg_cells\ex01413-202401_yg_cells.caproject" dateCreated="2024-02-22 16:05:45" lastModified="2024-03-13 13:23:11" limsExperiment="EX01413" />
    <experimentPointer projectType="DATA_ANALYSIS" id="4d0e1c52-250a-47ab-993a-d04858b8c14e" name="EX01355 - BATCH04-NEG-V2" description="MoTrPAC Human Tranche1 Muscle samples from shipment H20000820Y" experimentFile="y:\dataanalysis\mrc2toolboxprojects\_core\ex01355\ex01355-batch04-neg-v2\ex01355-batch04-neg-v2.caproject" dateCreated="2023-12-14 14:22:01" lastModified="2023-12-14 14:48:05" limsExperiment="EX01355" />
    <experimentPointer projectType="DATA_ANALYSIS" id="5dcc4dd2-4365-4fde-a779-b26c955c8167" name="EX01424 - Normalization for Inner Ear Samples II" description="As requested, these are 11 more additional test samples. &#xD;&#xA;Samples 1R, 2R, 3R, 4R, 4L, 5R and 5L are from a different WT mouse line.They are normal hearing mice, however, I wanted to note this.&#xD;&#xA;Samples 6-R; 6-L; 7-R; 7-L are from the same mouse line from roughly same age as the &amp;quot;actual&amp;quot; samples.&#xD;&#xA;I do not expect either the sidedness to substantially affect FA levels.&amp;quot;Would you happen to have 6-8 additional test samples I could try one more test on?  I reverted to the original solvent for the last of the 3 tests, instead of the recommended solvent for the Precellys, but I want to test the recommended solvent one more time (if you remember I said the fatty acids did not look good in test 1 and 2 with the recommended solvent, but we changed two things for test 3: the solvent type and the solvent volume, so I want to see which was the key change.)&amp;quot; - Maureen 2/15 Email to Gunseli" experimentFile="Y:\DataAnalysis\MRC2ToolboxProjects\_CORE\EX01424-Normalization-for-Inner-Ear-Samples-II\EX01424-Normalization-for-Inner-Ear-Samples-II.caproject" dateCreated="2024-05-06 20:47:50" lastModified="2024-05-06 20:47:50" limsExperiment="EX01424" />
    <experimentPointer projectType="DATA_ANALYSIS" id="b2ff9142-fa31-4ba8-b70e-5ed61034eec5" name="EX01404 - Energy metabolism in 18h mac effero (apopOB)" description="One of the first steps in osseous wound repair after trauma is cell death and subsequent apoptotic cell (AC) clearance (efferocytosis) by macrophages. Through efferocytosis, macrophages secrete a variety of factors that facilitate regeneration, and swiftly adapt their behavior in response to a range of physical and biological microenvironmental cues. To examine transcriptional changes in relation to efferocytosis, single-cell RNA sequencing (scRNA-seq) was performed on naive macrophages and efferocytic macrophages engulfing apoptotic osteoblasts. The scRNA-seq data consistently showed upregulation of glycolysis-associated genes in efferocytic macrophage clusters (also validated via qRT-PCR), indicating an enhancement of glycolytic pathways and a potential production of lactate in bone macrophages. Recent literature suggests shifts in metabolism and bioenergetics is associated with functional changes in macrophages, for instance increased glycolysis is linked with heightened inflammatory activity in macrophages. However, the efferocytosis-induced macrophage glycolysis has been recently associated with metabolic changes distinct from the glycolytic upregulation observed in inflammatory macrophages. In this context, it might accelerate the pro-resolving function of macrophages through a different mechanism. The aim of this experiment is to identify specific changes in bone macrophage metabolism induced by efferocytosis of apoptotic osteoblastic cells. To this end metabolic differences in macrophages cultured alone, macrophages co-cultured for 18h with apoptotic osteoblasts (1 AC per 1 macrophage), or apoptotic osteoblasts alone will be analyzed." experimentFile="Y:\DataAnalysis\MRC2ToolboxProjects\_CORE\EX01404-Energy-metabolism-in-18h-mac-effero-apopOB-\EX01404-Energy-metabolism-in-18h-mac-effero-apopOB-.caproject" dateCreated="2024-06-07 17:45:37" lastModified="2024-06-07 17:45:38" limsExperiment="EX01404" />
    <experimentPointer projectType="DATA_ANALYSIS" id="80ce9e87-ef14-41fa-ab4a-efd22fe893e6" name="EX01409 - BATCH01" description="MoTrPAC Human Post Suspension Tranche 1 EDTA plasma samples from shipment W20000960M" experimentFile="Y:\DataAnalysis\MRC2ToolboxProjects\_CORE\EX01409\EX01409-BATCH01\EX01409-BATCH01.caproject" dateCreated="2024-07-23 14:33:57" lastModified="2024-07-23 14:33:58" limsExperiment="EX01409" />
    <experimentPointer projectType="DATA_ANALYSIS" id="d9cd5b4f-3ef3-4ae6-b699-3c1d54b9a8ef" name="EX01421 - BA Flux WT VSG and Sham Exp" description="This study aims to assess the bile acid conversion in Sham and VSG mice. Mixed meal including isotope labeled bile acids CA, TCA and DCA were infused intraduodenally and bile acid composition assessed in plasma (0, 30, 60, 120 mins) and tissues (120 mins) post meal.We are evaluating bile acid conversion using isotope labeled bile acids.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;For each mouse, bile acid mix (D6-DCA, D5-CA, D4-TCA) was injected into proximal duodenum at time 0. At serial timepoints (0, 30, 60, 120 minutes) plasma was collected. At conclusion of experiment liver and duodenal chyme and cecal contents were collected (120 mins). &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Analysis we need: &#xD;&#xA;1)&#x9;Quantitative composition of each bile acid (raw data and area under curve)&#xD;&#xA;2)&#x9;Percent labeling or raw quantitative data of: CA, DCA, TCA, TDCA, CDCA, MCA.&#xD;&#xA;M0, M4, M5, M6 only&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;All bile acids D0&#xD;&#xA;CA-D0, CA-D5, TCA-D5, DCA-D5, TDCA-D5, CDCA-D5 and MCA-D5&#xD;&#xA;TCA-D0, CA-D4, TCA-D4, DCA-D4, TDCA-D4, CDCA-D4 and MCA-D4&#xD;&#xA;DCA-D0, CA-D6, TCA-D6, DCA-D6, TDCA-D6, CDCA-D6 and MCA-D6&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;We are not expecting significant D2, D3 etc labeling. We anticipate primarily seeing only our initial M4, M5, M6 species over the time course of the experiment. (For example, we don&amp;apos;t believe D4-TCA will be converted in significant amounts into M3, M2, etc species, but rather D4-TCA to become D4-CA and D4-DCA. Similarly, we expect direct interconversion of D5-CA to D5-DCA and D5-TCA, but expect relatively minor percents to convert to D4, D3, etc).  This is why we only need M0, M4, M5 and M6.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Quantification:&#xD;&#xA;We discussed this extensively with Maureen when designing this experiment. Because we have 3 interfering labeled species, the isotope labeled internal standard mix cannot be used for this experiment.  However, Maureen ran the analysis with us and raw data with external (separate run) standards can be used to quantify each species reliably. We need quantification of the composition (not just relative composition) for this study to work." experimentFile="Y:\DataAnalysis\MRC2ToolboxProjects\_CORE\EX01421-BA-Flux-WT-VSG-and-Sham-Exp\EX01421-BA-Flux-WT-VSG-and-Sham-Exp.caproject" dateCreated="2024-08-07 13:49:49" lastModified="2024-08-07 13:49:50" limsExperiment="EX01421" />
    <experimentPointer projectType="DATA_ANALYSIS" id="57af1393-b928-477a-9f99-8c96b38f1195" name="EX01409 - peakWidthTest" description="MoTrPAC Human Post Suspension Tranche 1 EDTA plasma samples from shipment W20000960M" experimentFile="Y:\DataAnalysis\MRC2ToolboxProjects\_CORE\EX01409\EX01409-peakWidthTest\EX01409-peakWidthTest.caproject" dateCreated="2024-08-09 14:48:14" lastModified="2024-08-09 14:48:15" limsExperiment="EX01409" />
    <experimentPointer projectType="DATA_ANALYSIS" id="b5f7bf83-2cbe-41a8-86c6-51e528645d33" name="EX01409-B2-dup-test" description="MoTrPAC Human Post Suspension Tranche 1 EDTA plasma samples from shipment W20000960M" experimentFile="Y:\DataAnalysis\MRC2ToolboxProjects\_CORE\EX01409\EX01409-B2-dup-test\EX01409-B2-dup-test.caproject" dateCreated="2024-08-09 20:14:33" lastModified="2024-08-09 20:14:34" limsExperiment="EX01409" />
    <experimentPointer projectType="DATA_ANALYSIS" id="1ceb9cce-8a46-4ff2-bab0-dd50afb9e728" name="EX01440 - ESM-40" description="Experimental Design: Mice will be separeted in 5 groups with sample collection in different time points after sepsis induction: Control, Sepsis day3, day21, day42 and day 63.  Blood samples will be collected from each mice and plasma separated and freezed for metabolomics. Overall Aim: Identify differential metabolites that are induced during sepsis and possible differences that are sustained long-term after sepsis. OBS: Note that Samples 17-24 are absent due to unantecipated events during experiment. Total number of samples is 40." experimentFile="Y:\DataAnalysis\MRC2ToolboxProjects\_CORE\EX01440-ESM-40\EX01440-ESM-40.caproject" dateCreated="2024-08-26 15:12:51" lastModified="2024-08-26 18:47:48" limsExperiment="EX01440" />
    <experimentPointer projectType="DATA_ANALYSIS" id="dc1f0b72-8f3b-43a7-b72f-209fb70dedf0" name="EX01470 - V1" description="The Preterm Nutrition &amp; Metabolism study is a prospective observational preterm mother-infant cohort from University of Michigan Brandon NICU. The study included infants born at &lt;34 weeks or &lt;1800 grams initially receiving  mother's own milk (MOM) or donor human milk (DHM) fortified with human milk (Prolacta) or bovine milk fortifiers (HMF- human milk fortifier, formula). Milk the infant is receiving is collected near 3 weeks of age and near discharge/40 weeks gestational age. Additional biospecimens include infant serum, infant urine, and infant stool samples at these two time points. The goal of this study is to evaluate the impact of milk composition on infant metabolomics profiles of nutrient processing, metabolomics, microbiome generation, intestinal maturation and infant growth patterns (weight, length, head circumference, skin folds, fat mass, fat free mass) in infant’s receiving preterm MOM and pasteurized DHM. The goal is to determine key components of human milk that drive improved infant developmental and growth outcomes and determine mechanisms to target for nutritional interventions for high risk infants." experimentFile="Y:\DataAnalysis\MRC2ToolboxProjects\_CORE\EX01470\EX01470-V1\EX01470-V1.caproject" dateCreated="2024-11-04 11:15:01" lastModified="2024-11-04 15:02:06" limsExperiment="EX01470" />
    <experimentPointer projectType="ID_TRACKER_DATA_ANALYSIS" id="IDX0257" name="EX01117-Heart-iDDA-POS-V2" description="Rerun of EX01117 (MoTrPAC) heart POS mode iDDA using Tracker data extraction" dateCreated="2024-02-21 15:12:30" lastModified="2024-02-21 15:12:30" limsExperiment="IDX0257" />
    <experimentPointer projectType="RAW_DATA_ANALYSIS" id="781a54bf-cf95-4365-bc34-259df4441358" name="EX00953-Heart-iDDA-POS-V2" description="Rerun of EX00953 (MoTrPAC) heart POS mode iDDA using Tracker data extraction" experimentFile="y:\dataanalysis\mrc2toolboxprojects\_idtracker\heart-v2\ex00953-heart-idda-pos-v2\ex00953-heart-idda-pos-v2.rdproject" dateCreated="2024-02-21 11:12:34" lastModified="2024-02-21 12:17:01" limsExperiment="IDX0255" createdBy="U00037" />
    <experimentPointer projectType="RAW_DATA_ANALYSIS" id="1970288d-c0a2-4ebb-b761-3baa4d8add25" name="EX00979-Liver-iDDA POS test" description="EX00979-Liver-iDDA positive mode test experiment" experimentFile="y:\dataanalysis\mrc2toolboxprojects\_idtracker\ex00979\ex00979-liver-idda-pos-test\ex00979-liver-idda-pos-test.rdproject" dateCreated="2023-02-08 19:07:40" lastModified="2023-04-19 12:49:31" createdBy="U00037" />
  </RecentExperiments>
</RecentObjects>
